

MA-336, College Ring 6, Bremen, 28759, Germany

□ (+49) 1511-5661770 | 🗷 theparthshukla@gmail.com | 🌴 www.parthshukla.xyz | 🕡 theparthshukla | 🛅 theparthshukla

"Do, or do not. There is no try."

Summary _

Creative and engaged first year Computer Science student with experience in design and web development. Interested in using my passion for problem solving to build better solutions for challenging tasks and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Education

Jacobs University

Bremen, Germany

Aug. 2019 - Present

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Work Experience _____

UWC Mahindra College

Pune,India

January. 2018, Mar. 2018 - January. 2019

- SECRETARY OF THE COLLEGE ASSEMBLY
- Facilitated, supported, and coordinated all activities of the student council. • Developed, promoted, and conducted a variety of extra curricular programs for students.
- · Organized and coordinated various fundraising programs and funfair events to generate revenue.
- Planned, arranged, and chaired all meetings with council members, as needed.

Leave No Fingerprints

Mumbai.India

WEB DEVELOPER AND GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Sep. 2018, Mar. 2017 - June. 2019

- Developed and maintained the front end functionality of websites.
- Devised SEO strategies based around specific keywords.

Ahmedabad Student Parliament

Ahmedabad,India

Duna India

HEAD OF IT AND LOGISTICS

Jun. 2017 - May. 2018

· Arranged and coordinated all on-site logistics, including transportation, accommodations, meals, guest speakers and audiovisual support. · Appointed and led a highly skilled IT team to create event infrastructure as well as provide support during the length of the events.

Honors & Awards

Dummar IIm TC CIT Wi-

rune,Inaia
nbai,India
elhi, India
kata,India
bad, India
bad, India
elhi, Ir kata,Ir bad, Ir

Skills_

Programming Experienced: JAVA, Python Basic:C, C++,

Tools Experienced:Git

Front-end Experienced: HTML5 Basic: REACT

Languages Native: English, Hindi Basic: Spanish, German

Extracurricular Activity

Computers for All

Pune, India

SERVICE PROGRAM CO-ORDINATOR

Aug. 2017 - Jan. 2019

· Set up a functional computer lab and gave basic computer education to people of all age groups in the village of Asade.

PARTH SHUKLA · RÉSUMÉ NOVEMBER 6, 2019